# **Charles Webb**

# Founder & Owner (Chief Game Developer) - Faux-Operative Games, LLC

Los Angeles, CA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Charles-Webb/04b32786ca511e95

A highly motivated tutor with five years of experience teaching SAT prep for Revolution and Catalyst. Creative, adaptable, productive under pressure, capable of meeting deadlines, and budget savvy. Known for increasing student scores by hundreds of points. Also co-owner of Faux-Operative games and creator of 'Ruin of the Reckless'

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Founder & Owner (Chief Game Developer)

Faux-Operative Games, LLC - Santa Barbara, CA - 2014 to Present

Planned and ran a successful kickstarter campaign; programmed Ruin of The Reckless, self taught and extremely capable in the GML programming language. Furnished deals with; Steam, Itch.io, GOG, and The Humble Store; managed all aspects of social marketing and social platforms; responsible for all website design, project design, art direction, and team/artist management; developed strong bonds with well-known indiegame developers, journalists, and streamers; work featured on PC Gamer, Rock Paper Shotgun, Indie Game Magazine, Co-Optimus, CG Mag Online, TotalBiscuits Co-optional Podcast, and more.

## **SAT Prep Tutor**

Catalyst Prep, Inc - Santa Barbara, CA - 2013 to 2014

Experienced tutor specializing in SAT prep; prepared low to high competency students for SAT; worked oneon-one with students at private in-home settings; led large groups of up to 30 students in classroom settings. Conducted online video conferences with small groups of students; achieved results and was able to routinely see a 200-300 point increase in test scores.

### **SAT Prep Tutor**

Revolution Prep, Inc - Santa Barbara, CA - 2011 to 2013

Tutored low to high competency students one on one, Tailored lesson plans to each student; worked in private in-home settings; routinely significantly increased student's SAT scores.

#### **Lead Technical Support Specialist**

MasterWriter, Inc - Santa Barbara, CA - 2008 to 2012

Worked for creative software company; handled inquiries from all users; managed and created a streamlined technical support system for resolving user issues quickly; led multiple sales conferences on behalf of the company; sold more units than any other presenter at a single conference(41 copies at \$149.00 over two 8 hour days.)

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **BA** in Communication in Communication

University of California - Santa Barbara, CA 2008

# SKILLS

Catalyst. (Less than 1 year)

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

## **SKILLS**

Familiarity with Revolution and Catalyst Prep course design.

Familiarity with both SAT and ACT coursework design.

High marks and reviews from students and co-workers.

Extensive experience tutoring high school students on SAT course material.